{
    "Differential Equations": {
      "Chapter 1: Introduction to Differential Equations": [
        {
          "question": "Solve for \\(x\\): \\(3x - 5 = 1\\)",
          "answer": "\\(x = 2\\)"
        },
        {
          "question": "Factor \\(x^2 - 5x + 6\\)",
          "answer": "\\((x - 2)(x - 3)\\)"
        }
      ],
      "Chapter 2: First-Order Differential Equations": [
        {
          "question": "Differentiate \\(f(x) = x^3\\)",
          "answer": "\\(f'(x) = 3x^2\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Chapter 3: Mathematical Models and Numerical Methods Involving First-Order Equations":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 4: Linear Second-Order Equations":[
        {

        }
      ],
      
      "Chapter 5: Introduction to Systems":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 6: Theory of Higher-Order Linear Differential Equations":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 7: Laplace Transforms":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 8: Series Solutions of Differential Equations":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 9: Matrix Methods for Linear Systems":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },














    "Linear Algebra": {
      "Chapter 1: Linear Equations in Linear Algebra": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Chapter 2: Matrix Algebra":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 3: Determinants":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 4: Vector Spaces":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 5: Eigenvalues and Eigenvectors":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 6: Orthogonality and Least Squares":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 7: Symmetric Matrices and Quadratic Forms":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },













    "Calculus III": {
      "Chapter 1: Vectors and the Geometry of Space": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],
      
      "Chapter 2: Vector-Valued Functions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 3: Functions of Several Variables":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 4: Multiple Integration":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 5: Vector Calculus":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },














    "Discrete Mathematics": {
      "Chapter 1: Logic and Proofs": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Chapter 2: Sets, Functions, Sequences, and Sums":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 3: Algorithms":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 4: Number Theory":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 5: Induction and Recursion":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 6: Counting":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 7: Discrete Probability":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 8: Advanced Counting Techniques":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 9: Relations":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 10: Graphs":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Chapter 11: Trees":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },













    "AP Calculus BC": {
      "Unit 1: Limits and Continuity": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Unit 2: Differentiation: Definition and Fundamental Properties":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 3: Differentiation: Composite, Implicit, and Inverse Functions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 4: Contextual Applications of Differentiation":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 5: Analytical Applications of Differentiation":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 6: Integration and Accumulation of Change":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 7: Differential Equations":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 8: Applications of Integration":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 9: Parametric Equations, Polar Coordinates, and Vector-Valued Functions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 10: Infinite Sequences and Series":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },
















    "AP Statistics": {
      "Unit 1: Exploring One-Variable Data": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Unit 2: Exploring Two-Variable Data":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 3: Collecting Data":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 4: Probability, Random Variables, and Probability Distributions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 5: Sampling Distributions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 6: Inference for Categorical Data: Proportions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 7: Inference for Quantitative Data: Means":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 8: Inference for Categorical Data: Chi-Square":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 9: Inference for Quantitative Data: Slopes":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },












    "AP Chemistry": {
      "Unit 1: Atomic Structure and Properties": [
        {
          "question": "Find \\(s\\) if \\(u = 0, a = 9.8, t = 2\\)",
          "answer": "\\(s = \\frac{1}{2}(9.8)(4) = 19.6\\,m\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Unit 2: Compound Structure and Properties":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 3: Properties of Substances and Mixtures":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 4: Chemical Reactions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 5: Kinetics":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 6: Thermochemistry":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 7: Equilibrium":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 8: Acids and Bases":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 9: Applications of Thermodynamics":[
        {

        }
      ]
    },















    "Honors Chemistry": {
      "Unit 1: Nature of Science": [
        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(9.07\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(3\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(12\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(2\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(1200.\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(4\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(0.03\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(1\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(1.003\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(4\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(1.00\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(3\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(0.02\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(1\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "How many significant figures are in \\(100\\)?",
          "answer": "\\(1\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Write \\(0.00007\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(7\\cdot 10^{-5}\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(420034\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(4.20034\\cdot 10^5\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Write \\(0.00450\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(4.50\\cdot 10^{-5}\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(123456\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(1.23456\\cdot 10^5\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(0.001\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(1\\cdot 10^{-3}\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(100.\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(1.00\\cdot 10^{2}\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Write \\(1000.\\) in scientific notation.",
          "answer": "\\(1.000\\cdot 10^3\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(3.1\\times 10^4\\) in floating decimal notation.",
          "answer": "\\(31000\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(2.48\\times 10^3\\) in floating decimal notation.",
          "answer": "\\(2480\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(1.000\\times 10^{-3}\\) in floating decimal notation.",
          "answer": "\\(0.001000\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Write \\(1.45\\times 10^6\\) in floating decimal notation.",
          "answer": "\\(0.00000145\\)"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Write \\(1.00\\times 10^2\\) in floating decimal notation.",
          "answer": "\\(100.\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Round \\(6080.4\\) to 3 significant figures.",
          "answer": "\\(6080\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "Round \\(6080.4\\) to 4 significant figures.",
          "answer": "\\(6080.\\)"
        },

        {
          "question": "\\( (2.3\\)cm)\\(4.007\\)cm)",
          "answer": "\\(9.2\\) cm\\(^2\\)"
        }
      ],

      "Unit 2: Atomic Structure and Energy of Electrons":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 3: Periodicity":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 4: Bonding and Compounds":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 5: Reactions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 6: Stoichiometry":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 7: VSPER/IMFs":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 8: States of Matter":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 9: Gas Laws":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 10: Solutions":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 11: Acids and Bases":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 12: Equilibrium":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 13: Thermochemistry":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 14: Nuclear Chemistry":[
        {

        }
      ],

      "Unit 15: Organic Chemistry":[
        {

        }
      ]
    }
  }